<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Copa America 24</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Copa America 24</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 14:15:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 14:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/day-2/</guid>
      
      <description>Day 2 Peru v Chile Boring. Wild shooting. The battle of the old pros still flying the flags end with a point. This was a match with so many old pros who were STILL playing for both these countries. And in the end, none of them could finish their chances because we only got a grand total of 5 shots on target. 4 from Peru and 1 from Chile which says to how stupid this game really was.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/day-1/</guid>
      
      <description>Day 1 Argentina v Canada The definition of toying with the opposition. Martinez brings his shooting boots from Milan. Canada goalie the lone bright spark in an underwhelming showing. An absolutely comfortable win for the holders Argentina as they were relatively comfortable and took their goals well. Let&amp;rsquo;s get into the reaction.
1st Half This half was good from Argentina. We got a chance as early as minute 5 with a shot from Acuna being blocked and Paredes blazing a shot over.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Brazil and Argentina</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/squads-brazil-argentina/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:21:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/squads-brazil-argentina/</guid>
      
      <description>Squad Reaction - Brazil and Argentina These guys are the main teams in this tournament even though you&amp;rsquo;ve got good talent in some teams, you really can&amp;rsquo;t go past these 2 to be the favorites. But I think Argentina are more higher favorites than Brazil because in my opinion this Brazil squad has taken a huge hit and without Neymar as well(I can understand it because he was mostly injured but still he&amp;rsquo;s a solid person to have in the dressing room for the youngsters), I think they have good quality with the likes of Vini Jr and Rodrygo and even Endrick.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groups</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:07:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/groups/</guid>
      
      <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duration</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/duration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:07:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-24/posts/duration/</guid>
      
      <description>Duration of Copa America June 21st - July 15th 2024</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
